# SAEID DOROUDI

Software Engineer

Tehran, IR | https://saeiddoroudi.ir +989144786806 | sdoroudi@mafpars.com

GitHub | LinkedIn | StackOverflow

Software engineer with 10+ years' experience in multiple businesses from small startups to manage software projects in large scale companies. Challenge lover and every day learner love to contribute to open-source projects and do more.

## **SKILLS**

- Back-End | C# | .Net | ASP.Net | OOP | SQL Server | Redis | NoSQL | Testing | RabbitMQ | CI/CD | Docker | Kubernetes
- Front-End | JavaScript | TypeScript | Vue.js | PWA | React | jQuery | HTML | CSS | Angular | Ionic | Blazor | Flutter | SSR/SSG.
- Micro-Services | DDD | Azure | Git | Scrum | K6 | OAuth | GraphQL | gRPC | Speck in Turkish, Persian and English.

# **EXPERIENCES**

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

HyperStar(MafPars) | Tehran

2021 - PRESENT

- Building multiple back-office applications for multiple parts of organization such as HR, eCommerce, Finance and Suppliers to achieve up to 40% cost saving and digitalizing manual process.
- Building Customers Loyalty mobile application (Flutter) and lottery system to make customers loyal and have better experience.
- Building scalable microservices based on .Net and use Kubernetes as Infrastructure for achieving zero down time deployment.
- Integrate DB2 based system that doesn't provide real-time update with Online shopping channels like Snapp Shop, Digikala.
- Providing Supplier Portal and integrate it with BPMS software, gains lot of cost and paper saving with automating ordering.
- Find performance bottlenecks using Performance Testing, implement test processes for critical business sections using BDD.
- Implement Front-End infrastructure using Vue.Js 3 and TypeScript and update all front-end apps to new structure.

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Mobinnet | Tehran

2018 - 2021

- Build Mobinnet eCare Mobile app using PWA and Asp.Net Core, Vue which responds to more than 70% of requests beside web
  version after a little while.
- Find Performance issues and design new structure for existing eCare System using .Net Core, CQRS, Redis, Kafka, HA Proxy, Azure DevOps witch results in 99.999% uptime system.
- Implement Modem Troubleshoot application using Ionic to help customers to find and fix their internet connectivity issues.

#### MOBILE DEVELOPER

ArtinMehr | Tabriz

2017 - 2018

Build 3 Ionic based shopping mobile applications for local shopping centers and deploy them to Google Play and AppStore.

#### **CO-FOUNDER, DEVELOPER**

Elca | Marand

2015 - 2017

- Build SMS based Lottery System for food industry factories and build simpler version for restaurants using Asp.Net and Angular.
- Build TeleHub (Telegram Directory App) Mobile Application and Service and publish it to AppStore and Windows Store.
- Build Iran Football League Mobile app using Java and publish it to Bazaar and reach thousands active users.
- Implement Factory Production process management WinForms based system for customer (SahandZoob).
- Implement Telegram bots for controlling IoT based systems based on Raspberry Pl.
- Building multiple IoT based applications and RFID based entrance control systems.

FREELANCER 2007 – 2013

- Build Abna-News Agency QA Multilingual (5 Languages) website.
- Build Application for managing Tax for municipality of Marand.
- Build Websites and Applications for BlogSky, IranArmy, Tabriz University, Hoopa, Barayand Publishing, and many other clients.
- Build ThemeStudio website and sell blog themes and get orders to develop Websites.

### **EDUCATION**